http://thepilgrimpress.com/pages/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY AND DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACT NOTICE
This privacy policy explains the privacy practices of the National Setting of the United Church of Christ (“the UCC”) as applied through thepilgrimpress.com and how the UCC treats your information that is gathered through thepilgrimpress.com.
This policy only applies to information we collect from visitors to our website, thepilgrimpress.com.  This policy does not apply to information collected by the UCC offline, through any other website maintained by the UCC, or through any other means, or from any third party.  Please read this privacy policy carefully.  You acknowledge that it is part of our terms and conditions.  If you do not agree, you must not access thepilgrimpress.com, use any of the content found on thepilgrimpress.com, or make any purchases from thepilgrimpress.com.
The UCC collects the personal information that you make available to the UCC, including first and last name, email address, phone number, user name, passwords, and cookie data.  Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through thepilgrimpress.com, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number.  We do not store your payment information as payments are processed through Shopify.  Please see below for a link to Shopify’s privay policy.  We also collect some information automatically about your computer hardware and software, which can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and dates, referring website addresses, cookies, flash cookies, web beacons, and log file information.  The information that we automatically collect does not by itself identify a specific individual and is statistical data typically aggregated with other data to help us improve our website.  The UCC collects your information when you make a purchase; when you provide consent; for purposes that are required by law; and for the purposes of responding to requests by the government, a court of law, or law enforcement authorities conducting an investigation.
The UCC uses your information to present our website and its contents to you; to communicate with you via emails to which you subscribe; to fulfill contracts, in particular, facilitating and processing purchases and related transactions; and where it is necessary to fulfill the UCC’s legitimate interests, which include operating our website; providing information and goods and services described on our website; verifying your identity; determining how to improve our website; and responding to your questions and comments.
The UCC shares your information with third parties to help us use your information.  For example, we use Shopify to power our online store—you can read more about how Shopify uses your information here:  https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use thepilgrimpress.com—you can read more about how Google uses your personal information here:https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
The UCC retains your personal information for as long as necessary to provide the services to you and to comply with legal obligations. You can obtain a copy of the personal information maintained by the UCC by clicking here.  You can modify or request that the UCC delete your personal information by logging in here; however, the UCC will retain information as is necessary for the UCC’s legitimate business interests.  If you are unable to access your data by clicking the links in the previous statements, please send an email to pilgrim@ucc.org.  If you have questions about the UCC’s privacy practices, please contact Heather E. Kimmel at kimmelh@ucc.org.
The UCC reserves the right to change our website and this privacy policy, at our discretion.  When any change is made, a revised version will be posted here and will be effective as of the revised date.
Please notify the UCC if you believe that any of your intellectual property rights have been infringed.  Pursuant to Section 512 of the Copyright Act (“DMCA”), the UCC designates the following individual as its agent for receipt of notifications of claimed infringement:  United Church of Christ, Heather Kimmel, General Counsel, kimmelh@ucc.org, 700 Prospect Ave. E., Cleveland, OH 44115.  To be effective, the notification should include:  a physical or electronic signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the right being infringed; identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at the site; identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity, and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; information sufficient to allow us to contact the complaining party; a statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that the use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright or intellectual property owner, agent, or the law; and a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the right being infringed.  If you fail to comply with all of these requirements, your DMCA notification may not be valid.
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
